Well, if you think logically at all, then
Ну если логически вообще мыслить да то
he initially recognized Donetsk Lugansk
он признал изначально вот Донецк Луганск
Well, the Donetsk People's Republic and the
Ну донецкую народную Республику и
Lugansk People's Republic And after
луганскую народную Республику И после
that you started attacking them and we
этого вы начали атаковать их и мы
answered Well, it's logical then it turns out
ответили Ну это логично тогда получается
you attacked and not us, yes, that is, it turns out
вы напали а не мы да то есть получается
that And we attacked Yes  on
что А мы напали Да на
you not on us on our allies with
вас не на нас на наших союзников с
whom we entered into an agreement That is,
которым мы заключили соглашение То есть
you could not attack
вы могли не нападать
Hello Hello, I’m from the city of
Здравствуйте Здравствуйте я из города
Khmelnitsky Where are you
Хмельницкий Вы
from from Moscow and to Moscow Where did you
откуда из Москвы а в Москву Откуда
come from did not come born here And
приехали не приезжал родился здесь А
the parents of the grandparents Where did
родители бабушки дедушки Откуда в Москву
they come to Moscow from Well, grandfather, well there
приехали Ну дедушка ну там история такая
you know the story Well, a little personal Yes in terms of
вы знаете Ну немножко личная Да в плане
everything That’s it and we’ll end with this Yes just
всё Вот так и на этом закончим Да просто
where I’m from Moscow I’m talking grandfather
откуда Я из Москвы Я говорю дедушка
from not like he Moved from but just
откуда не как он Переезжал а просто
from from Russia Belarus Ukraine Tamm
откуда из России белорусси Украины тамм
region
области
Well, well, I don’t have exact information so to
Ну ну точной информации у меня нет так
speak  I understand How do you communicate? It
скажем понял А чем общаетесь
depends on what topic it suggests
ту смотря какую тему предлагает
if you ask I will
если задавать Я
support mos mo I usually ask people from
поддержу мос мо Я спрашиваю людей из
Russia how do you feel about the fact
России обычно как вы относитесь к тому
that Russia attacked
что Россия напала на
Ukraine
Украину
Well look From what point of view are you from from
Ну смотр С какой точки зрения вы с с
your point of view
вашей точки зрения
the answer That’s why I’m asking you  I’m
отве Я же у вас спрашиваю поэтому мне
interested in your point of
интересна ваша точка
view,
зрения
well, it seems like a
хорошо влом каже
tool for making money for
инструмент зарабатывания денег для
certain people,
определенных людей
and it so happened that now these
и вот так получилось что вот сейчас эти
people are making money inside our
люди зарабатывают деньги внутри нашего
Slavic world and I would in
Славянского мира и мне бы ни в коем
no way want this to
случае не хотелось бы то что это
happen further And in general, in principle,
происходило дальше И вообще в принципе
it began Well  since it happened this way, then
начиналось Ну раз уж так сложилось то
again
опять
because, well, if a
потому что ну если внутри вашего
coup begins inside your state, well,
государства начина переворот Ну вы
our state will suffer for the
пострадает нашего государства на
coup. Well, actually, I don’t agree,
переворот Ну собственно говоря не соглас
so let’s say to reproduce it, then we will
так скажем воспроизводить то мы
suffer and of course none of us
пострадаю и само собой Никто из нас
did this, they don’t want to do this, they won’t
этого не сдела не хочет этого сделать не
do it in
сделат в
principle  in
принципе в
Ukraine, we can make a coup in Ukraine,
Украине мы переворот в Украине можем
we can spit, we know how to do it, like yes,
сделать плюнуть мы это умеем типа да
the question is, why should we do a coup? Russia did
вопрос Зачем нам делать переворот Россия
n’t attack you, our country.
нала не наша страна напала на
Well, as I understand, now you are happy with everything.
вас Ну я так понимаю что сейчас вас всё
Yes, we are not happy that Russia attacked,
Да нас не устраивает что Россия напала
well, we are not happy that Russia attacked  We were
ну нас не устраивает что Россия на нас
attacked. It doesn’t depend on our government,
напала Это же не от наше власти зависит
it depends on yours that you
это от вашей зависит что вы
attacked. Or did I somehow
напали Или я как-то не так вас
misunderstand you? Look, you said. Yes, some
понял Смотри вы сказали Да что какие-то
people, can you name those people who
люди то можете назвать тех людей которые
started this
развязали эту
war, well, those who now have money?
войну ну те которые сейчас имеют деньги
Yes  Well, who's behind the surname Feler
Да ну вот кто за коре фамилия фелер
Obama Who's
Обама Кто
who Well, in my opinion, yes You said one of
кто Ну на мой взгляд да Вот Вы одну из
the surnames yes And that,
фамилий произнесли да И это ну в том
among other things, Name the surname You
числе Назовите вы фамилию Фамилию вы
name the surname Name the surname
Назовите вы фамилию
Name it Well, bankers, if I say it so rudely, to be
Назовите Ну банкиры если так грубо
honest, I won’t say Well, in
сказать честно говоря не скажу Ну в
general  Are you afraid of these people? Why should
целом Вы что боитесь этих людей Зачем
I tell you my last name at all? Well, I’m
мне фамилию говорить вам вообще Ну мне
interested in understanding the meaning of these people. But I’m
интересно понять эти людей смыс Но мне
wondering who this person is who is
интересно кто этот человек который
to blame for this
виноват в этой
war, so I won’t tell you these names verbatim.
войне так дословно эти фамилии вам не
Well, you named Rockefeller. Yes, here’s
назову Ну Рокфеллер вы назвали Да вот
one. I’m afraid of distorting his last name.
одну Я боюсь там исковеркать его фамилию
Well.  including who was working now
Ну вот в том числе кто занимался сейчас
who Morgan you said well Morgan
кто Морган вы сказали ну Морган
Rockefeller Yes who
Рокфеллер Да кто
else Soros well bankers In
ещё сорос ну банкиры В
general why am I doing this comedy you
общем зачем вот эту комедию устраиваю вы
know them yourself the American bankers the
их сами знаете вот американские банкиры
founders in principle here is the banking
основатели в принципе вот банковская
system they are now making money from this
система они сейчас заработаю на этом
including  By the way, in the
деньги в том числе и кстати говоря вот
American way, this is the same as in America, again,
американски тя этоже чт в Америку опять
this money was not allowed in Europe. So
же эти деньги хотя в Европе не пустили
they also give
Вот и они точно также там дают кредиты
certain loans there, well, including in
определённые вот ну в том числе в
Ukraine now, and all the money, in principle,
Украине сейчас и все деньги в принципе
well, how does this system work and how do
ну как вот эта система действует да как
they say  I can speak so rudely, but I
О сказат я могу так грубо говорить но я
believe in it and I think that it
в это верю и я так считаю что о
really happens because
действительно происходит потому что
when they give money on credit,
когда дают деньги в кредит
they are initially uh determined to have
они изначально ээ расположены в том
this money handed over to them with interest,
чтобы им сдали эти деньги с процентами
that is, well, including they earn
то есть ну в том числе они зарабатывают
money
деньги
if in the country  he needs to produce weapons, he
если в стране нужно произвести оружие он
takes out a loan from the bank Yes, and then she needs to
берёт кредит в банке Да и потом ей нужно
return even more money to the bank,
вернуть ещё больше денег в банк
isn’t that right? I
получается разве не так я правильно Я
understood your logic correctly that these
правильно понял вашу логику что эти
world bankers forced Putin to
банкиры мировые заставили Путина
specifically attack Ukraine in order to
специально напасть на Украину чтобы
make money from it
зарабатывать на этом деньги
Yes, yes, it will work out, that is  Putin is a protege of
Да да получатся то есть Путин ставленник
these bankers.
этих банкиров
Well, they provoked a certain
Ну они определённую вот спровоцировали
situation and to which Putin was forced to
ситуацию и на что Путин был вынужден
react once again, look, we
отреагировать ещё раз смотрите вот мы
lived for ourselves, Ukraine lived, yes And then Putin
себе жили Украина жила да И тут Путин
attacks Ukraine. That is, it was Putin who
нападает на Украину То есть это Путин
attacked, or if these bankers are to blame,
напал или если эти банкиры виноваты
then it is the bankers who forced Putin, they are
значит это банкиры заставили Путина они
there  for example, they said We will cut off your
там например сказали Мы тебе отрежем
right
право
If you don’t attack Ukraine and he does
Если ты не напад на Украину и он такой
n’t, I want to be with two attacked Yes, how
нет я хочу быть с двумя напал Да как как
was it, how did they force
это было как они заставили
Putin Well, there are certain red
Путина Ну есть ну определённые красные
lines Yes, Putin has said more than once about them that
линии Да Путин не раз о них говорил что
he doesn’t like him  NATO's advance
вот он ему не нравится продвижение НАТО
to the east And when
на восток И когда в Украине произошёл
a coup d'état took place in Ukraine Well, in my
государственный переворот Ну на мой
opinion, we, if you want, If you don't
взгляд мы если хотите Если вы так не
think so, then we'll talk about it, well,
считаете потом об этом поговорим да ну
if you think that, well,
если вы считаете что ну
then Naturally, he understood that Ukraine
тогда Естественно он понимал что Украина
was striving to join NATO, that there would be
стремится в НАТО что там будут стоять
bases there for him  I don’t like this Well, in
базы ему это не нравится Ну и собственно
fact, there was a
говоря произошёл вот
certain conflict
определённый конфликт
and Wait, look, it turns out Putin Putin
и Подожди смотри получается Путин Путин
could not attack Ukraine and not the Slavs
мог не нападать на Украину и не славян
now Putin of the Slavs and Russian and
сейчас Путин славян и российских и
Ukrainian Slavs, yes, it turns out, that
славян украинских да получается да то
is, it turns out
есть получается
that he took and went on a leash to provoke
что он взял и пошл на поводке провокации
these bankers Yes  and started the war
этих банкиров Да и взял начал войну
Putin started the war
Путин же начал войну
like this Well, if you think logically at all,
так Ну если логически вообще мыслить да
then he initially recognized Donetsk
то он признал изначально вот Донецк
Lugansk the Donetsk People's Republic and the
Луганск донецкую народную Республику и
Lugansk People's Republic And after
луганскую народную Республику И после
that you began to attack them and we did it personally and
этого вы начали атаковать их
we attacked Yes,
а мы напали Да на
not on us, on ours  allies with
вас не на нас на наших союзников с
whom we entered into an agreement That is,
которым мы заключили соглашение То есть
you could not attack, listen
вы могли не нападать вот послушайте
please, I don’t know what his name is
пожалуйста я не знаю как как его зовут
and
ан
droni What is your name
дрони Как вас зовут
Andronik Lugansk Crimea is part of Ukraine and in the
Андроник Луганск Крым части Украины и
dream of moons Crimea course Bryansk Voronezh
сне лун Крым курс Брянск Воронеж
Krasnodar and Rostov are part of
Краснодар и Ростов частью
Ukraine these are our ancestral lands they are from
Украины это наши исконные земли они из
from time immemorial they were Ukrainian
покон веков были украино
yes So listen
да Так слушай
further if
дальше если
you would like to return them, you have two
ти как бы вы хотели их вернуть у вас два
options, you or the military pumas
варианта есть вы ите военным пум их
return them to the children, thus prosper
возвращаете дете таким образом процветай
your country inside, well, it is prospering I don’t
свою страну внутри ну процветает Я не
know, go to the European Union there they let you in
знаю идёте в Евросоюз там вас пустили
there you have Excellent in general  goods I don’t
там у вас Отличный вообще товары Я не
know excellent salaries they themselves will want to
знаю отличные зарплаты они сами захотят
leave You Propaganda works like this that
уйти У вас Пропаганда так работает что у
everything is bad in our country in Russia
нас в стране всё плохо в России
you know people themselves will leave for you Why
понимаете люди сами уйдут к вам Почему
don’t you go this way Why are you going to
вы этим путём не идёте Почему вы идёте
war on uh I don’t know chickens How not Kursk
войной на э я не знаю кур Как нет Курск
look  Kursk, you are going to war, you are
смотрите Курск это вы идёте войной вы
now bombing Kursk I don’t know better.
сейчас бомби Курск Я не знаю лучше Вот
How would you develop so that Kursk
вы бы как развивались чтобы Курск
would want to come back to you? Why are you
захотел сам к вам вернуться Почему вы
bombing Kursk, you are now dropping
бомбить Курск вы сейчас скидывает
air bombs on the Kursk region, you
авиационные бомбы на курскую область
understand, you are fighting in Kursk, you are not
понимаете вы воюете на Курск не вы на
fighting in Kursk, look, you attacked  on Don’t
Курск воюете смотрите Вы напали на Не
look Donetsk Lugansk these are our
смотрите Донецк Луганск это наши
territories you We were attacked you attacked
территории вы На нас напали вы напали на
our Kursk region even our Voronezh
нашу курскую область даже на наш Воронеж
our Krasnodar our Rostov
на наш Краснодар на наш Ростов
was occupied let’s say I’m not with
оккупировали допустим я не с
your Lenin your Lenin when you look
ваш Ленин ваш Ленин когда смотрите взял
Lenin took it when he created your Russian
Ленин когда создал вашу Российскую
Federation he took a part from Ukraine  its
Федерацию забрал у Украины часть её
territories and gave it to you Lenin
территорий и отдал вам подарил Ленин
gave you the Bryansk region Kursk
подарил вам брянскую область курскую
region Belgorod was the Belgorod
область Белгород был Белгородскую
region Yes the Rostov region the
область Да Ростовскую область
Voronezh region and the entire Krasnodar
воронежскую область и весь Краснодарский
region these are our lands and we are taking back ours
край это наши земли и мы забираем своё
we together with NATO are the Anglo-Saxons they have
мы вместе с НАТО это англосакс они
been with us since ancient times Yes with Russia our
издревле были с нами Да с Русью нашими
allies A
союзниками А
you were
вы эти были
andropharm
андрофарм
bomb Slavic cities
бомби славянские города
you follow the lead of Morgan
вы идёте на поводу морганов
Rockefeller that's why Putin has
рокфеллеров вот так почему Путин имеет
gas oil diamonds people live there Why is it like
там Газ Нефть алмазы люди живут Почему
this Because because Putin
так вот так Потому что потому что Путин
takes oil gas diamonds from all your
забирает нефть газ алмазы у всех ваших
people gives it to Morgan gives it to Rockefeller
людей отдаёт моргану отдаёт рокфеллеру
Yes they have all the money  pumped into British
Да все деньги они выкачали в британские
banks Do you know where your fund is? Why was
банки Ты знаешь где ваш этот фонд Почему
yours seized? Your gold and foreign exchange
арестовали ваш ваши золотовалютные
reserves were not in the banks of Morgan and
резервы ни были в банках Моргана и
Rockefeller,
рокфеллера
but who sent them there?
правда кто их туда отправил
Putin, no. And
Путин нет А
who? Well, because we lost the Cold
кто Ну потому что Мы проиграли холодную
War, they wrote us a
войну они написали нам Конституцию
definite Constitution that, in principle,
определённую что в принципе наш
it is our Central Bank  not subject to
Центробанк он не подвластен
Putin, the Central Bank minds its own
Путину Центробанк занимается своими
affairs, they are given
делами им дают международный банк
certain consultations by an international bank Yes, they are
определённые консультации Да ини туда
investing this money there Putin
эти деньги вкладывают Путин ничего
can’t do anything here stop stop stop Who
сделать тут не может стоп стоп стоп Кто
appoints the head of your
у вас назначает главу Кто у вас главу
Central Bank Who appoints the head of the Central Bank?  I
Центробанка назначает
generally agreed to Putin’s story if he had
вообще вот на историю Путина если бы он
initially told them his plan, if
изначально им рассказал свой план если
we want to get rid of this
мы хотим избавиться вообще от этой
Anglo-Saxon dependence altogether, that we, in
англосаксонской зависимости что мы в
principle, will move away from them. Well, now I
принципе там от них отойдём Ну сейчас я
’ll say, then you’ll say okay. You’ve been talking for a long time.
скажу потом вы скажете хорошо Вы долго
Yeah, we’ll move away from this now.
говорили Угу мы сейчас от этого отойдём
And that’s it  yours, you won’t have oligarchs Yes,
И всё ваши у вас не будет олигархов Да
all this sold national
вот это всё проданное национальное
property will return to statehood, it’s
достояние вернётся в государственность у
not coming back to us. For example, in our
нас возвращается не Например у нас в
country it came back to you, I don’t know,
стране это вернулось у вас не знаю
to be honest, I wasn’t interested,
честно говоря не интересовался может
maybe yes, maybe not,
быть да может быть нет
okay, the Ukrainians, I think they would
хорошо украинцы Мне кажется бы
agree, but live  in the Bosom of Russia
согласились Да вот жить в Лона России
Initially, these Anglo-Saxons would have placed them
Изначально и поставили бы эти англа
far and long and would not have started a
сакса далеко и надолго и не развязали
war here with us. I understood correctly that
здесь войну у нас Я правильно понял что
you
у вас в
no longer have oligarchs in Russia, the oligarchs
России олигархов уже нет у олигархов
took the Armed Forces’ property back to the state.
забрали ВС имущество назад в государство
Yes, name the oligarch you mean, I
Да Назовите олигарх какого имеете в виду
don’t know, Kovalchuk Rotenberg  Alisher
не знаю ковальчуки ротенберги Алишер
Usmanov
Усманов
Deripaska
Дерипаска
Malofeev I was
Малофеев я по большей
mostly interested in Yes, Gazprom and I
сти интересовался Да газпромом и я
was interested in
интересовался
how God bless him, this
и как его дай Бог памяти ну этот
former Abramovich, yes it turns out so
Абрамович бывший да получается так
look not all Abramovich left Ukraine a long time ago
смотри не все Абрамович давным-давно ещё
oh from Russia look
уехал из Украины ой из России смотри
really Yes all your oligarchs Yes Usmanov
реально Да все ваши олигархи Да Усманов
all  metallurgy is held there, and Deripaska is
всю металлургию держит да там Дерипаска
also there, these factories there are Nike or steel, and so
тоже заводы эти там Нике или стали и так
on,
дальше
the Rotenbergs, these Kovalchuks, everything is what
ротенберги эти ковальчуки все есть что
you are telling me here about these that without
ты мне заливаешь тут про эти что без
oligarchs are funny in short. Okay, let's move
олигархов смешные короче Хорошо давай
on.
дальше
The Central Bank of the Americans wrote
Центробанк вам американцы написали
some kind of Constitution for you. Who appoints
какую-то Конституцию Кто у вас назначает
the head of the Central Bank for you?
главу Центробанка на
Bible I don’t understand Who in your country appoints the head of the
библи Не понял Кто у вас назначает главу
question Who in Russia appoints
вопрос Кто у вас в России назначает
the head of the National Bank of the Central Bank in Bibu
главу Нацбанка Центробанка на Бибу
which is now in Bibu Yes, your authorities
которая сейчас на Бибу Да власти ваши
or the Americans from abroad are
или американцы изза границы
yours, so stop, then it means that it was not
ваши так то стоп то значит вам не
the Anglo-Saxons who appointed you the head of the Central Bank, but
англосакс назначили главу Центробанка а
Putin. What difference does it make?  our Constitution
Путин А какая разница у нас Конституции
is written properly that the Central Bank is
написано должным образом что Центробанк
not subordinate to the authorities,
не подчиняется власти
it is written to the international fund Open,
он международному фонду написано Открой
I’m opening now I’m opening your
я сейчас открываю ва Я открываю вашу
Constitution, come on, tell me where
Конституцию давай скажи мне где
You’re probably an adept, you’re probably an Adept,
Ты наверное адеп ты наверно Адепт
but you’re Fedorov and
но ты фёдорове да
Nodov
нодов
[music]
[музыка]
understood, yes, the Central Bank is not
понял да Центробанк не подчиняется
directly subordinate to either the president or  to the government
напрямую ни президенту ни правительству
or parliament, this is independently
ни парламенту это самостоятельно
enshrined in the Constitution of the Russian Federation and federal
закреплён Конституции РФ и федеральном
legislation. Who appoints the head of
законодательстве Кто назначает главу
the Central Bank
Центробанка
does not
не
appoint does not appoint you correctly
назначает не назначает вы правильно
said it, well, the state makes no difference.
сказали это ну государство разницы нет
What difference does it make?
Какая нет какая разница власти если ему
Now, if you look again Where
смотри вот если у ещё раз смотри Где у
in your Constitution it says that the Central Bank
вас в Конституции сказано что Центробанк
is subordinate to some Anglo-Saxon and
подчиняется каким-то англосакс и
obeys the unlock
слушается анлок
please now yes moment Yes, I’m
прошу сейчас да момент Да мне ж
interested, I’ll open it now Maybe it’s
интересно я сейчас открою Может
really just a bank, look The bank is a
действительно просто банк смотри Банк -
structure It’s just not in the
это структура Просто она не есть в
non-legislative structure  power, not
структуре не законодательной власти не
this, not executive, not judicial Yes,
этой не исполнительной не судебной Да
just like the plant director, here Gazprom is a
так же как завод директор вот Газпром
state structure Yes, but
государственная Да структура Да вот но
it is not presidential power, it is not a
она не президентская власть не это не
legislator, so
законодатель так
now You are right Come on, where are your
сейчас Вы правы Да ну давай где у вас
Constitutions? Yes, the Bank of
Конституции Да вот Банк
Russia is subject to the rules of the
России подчиняется правилам
international
международного
monetary system Well, of course  So come on, Article
валютного Ну само собо Вот давай статья
75 of the Constitution, read read Article 75 of the
75 Конституции читай читай статья 75
Constitution
Конституции
establishes that the monetary unit in
устанавливает что денежные единице в
our country is the ruble Well, it also
нашей стране является рубль Ну а также
determines the function of the Central Bank in
определяет функция Центробанка в
relation to the Russian So you open it,
отношени Российской Так ты открой не Ты
look, you read something about it,
смотри ты читаешь что-то про это ты
open the Constitution itself, you read the
открой саму Конституцию Ты читаешь че
description  read the first paragraph I opened the
описа читай первый пункт Я открыл се
fifth article read Oh well, I’m just
пятую статью читай А ну я просто это
Yandex now let’s yeah the
Яндекс сейчас давайте Ага
monetary unity in the Russian Federation
денежной единст в Российской Федерации
is the ruble the monetary mission
является рубль денежная миссия
is carried out exclusively by the central
осуществляется исключительно центральным
bank of the Russian Federation the introduction and
банком Российской Федерации введение и
mission of other money in Russia found the
миссия других денег в России нашли
first mention of the Central Bank we are looking for
первое упоминание про Центробанк ищем
where else where  it is said that he
ещё где где же сказано что он
obeys this. Let's
подчиняется этим Давай
look for it. Why should it be in the seventy-fifth article?
ищи Почему в семьдесят пятой статье
In principle, I
должно быть вообще в принципе я тебе для
found it for you as an example. Find Here, somewhere else there is a
примера нашёл Найди Вот где-то ещё
mention in the Constitution of the Central Bank.
упоминание в Конституции Центробанка
I suspect that there is no such thing there, and that
Я подозреваю что там такого нету да что
he is
он
subordinate to the Anglo-Saxons. Right now,
подчиняется англосаксов Я прямо сейчас
here is your entire Constitution  I’ll
вот всю Конституцию вашу
look at the foundations of the Constitution there, the
просмотрю не основы там Конституции
basis of dadada Come on,
основа дадада Давай Конституции
here’s Article 83 of the Constitution Yes, the President of the
вот статья 83 ещё Да президент
Russian Federation now presents to the
Российской Федерации вот представляет
State Duma a candidacy for the
Государственной думе кандидатуру на
appointment of the post of Chairman of the
назначение должность председателя
Central Bank of the Russian Federation
Центрального банка Российской Федерации
raises before the State Duma the
ставит перед государственнной думой
question of vacating the post of
вопрос об освобождении должности
Chairman of the Bank of the Russian Federation, the
председателя банка Российской Федерации
second mention we came across is so that
второе упоминание мы встретили так то
is, by  The president appoints the Constitution,
есть по Конституции президент назначает
not the Anglo-Saxon. But the president is looking further. Where is
не англосакс А президент дальше ищем Где
the Anglo-Saxon telling something to
же там англосакс что-то рассказывают
the central bank? The meaning of what you are saying is appointing.
центробанку смысл вы говорите назначает
What difference does it make who the leadership is now
Какая разница кто руководства сейчас
now now further further further
сейчас сейчас дальше дальше дальше
the main thing is to whom it is
главное кому
subordinated. Come on, article article
подчиняется Давай дальше статья статья
article 103k belongs to the jurisdiction of the State
статья 103к к ведению Государственной
Duma like this So in that  including the
Думы относится так Так в том числе
appointment to the position of vacating the
назначение на должности освобождения
position of the chairman of the Central
должности председателя Центрального
Bank of the Russian Federation, but
банка Российской Федерации но
there are no Anglo-Saxons anywhere here. Where are
англосаксов нету тут нигде Где ж про
the Anglo-Saxons in the
англосаксов в
bank in the Constitution? I opened your
банке в Конституции Я открыл вашу
Constitution. I’m just a lawyer by
Конституцию Я просто юрист по
training.
образованию м
Let’s see now,
давайте сейчас
you obviously haven’t read everything in the Constitution,
это вы видно не читали всё в Конституции
there is a mention of the Central Bank only in
упоминание Центробанка есть только в
three
трёх
articles in only three articles Yes, in
статьях только в трёх статьях Да в
article 75, where about the issue of the ruble in
статье 75 там где про эмиссию рубля в
article three, that the president submits to the
статье третьей что президент вносит
State Duma a candidacy for the
Государственной думе кандидатуру на
head of the Central Bank and dismisses the head of the Central Bank from
главу Центробанка и освобождает от
office and in the
должности главу Центробанка и реть
article that your State Duma deputies are not
статье что Госдума депутаты ваши не
Anglo-Saxons And your deputies appoint
англосакс А ваши депутаты назначают
the head of the chairman of the Central Bank
главу председателя Центрального банка
everything  there is nothing else in the Constitution about the
всё больше в Конституции ничего про
National Bank about your Central Bank
Национальный банк про Центробанк ваш
that it should listen to some kind of
нету что он должен слушать каких-то там
international
международные
relations now the Supreme
отношения
Court, it’s just that in life everything is just
сечас ВС просто в жизни всё просто
opening the Constitution and reading you are
открываешь Конституцию и читаешь ты
listening to someone but right
слушаешь кого-то но
Sorry, wait
пра Извините подождите
Yes, the generally accepted norms of International
Да общепризнанные нормы Международного
Law international international
права международного международные
treaties of the Russian  Federations are an
договоры Российской Федерации являются
integral part of its legal system Yes,
составной частью её правовой системы Да
this is what international law will
вот то что международное право нам
tell us, what we will do turns out
скажет то что мы будем делать получается
yes if an international treaty is an
да если международным договором
agreement Yes, other rules are established
договором Да установлены иные правила
than those provided for by law
чем предусмотрены законом
will apply about the Central Bank, tell me again
применятся про Центробанк скажи ещ раз
about the Central Bank I understand that you
про Центробанк Я понимаю что ты
have read a lot of Fedorov there you are for me  said that
начитался Фёдорова там ты мне сказал что
the Central Bank was adopted for you, they wrote the
Центробанк вам приняли вам написали
Constitution, it was you who said it with your mouth, not
Конституцию это ты своим ртом сказал Не
me That you lost the Cold War and they
я Что вы проиграли холодную войну и вам
wrote you a Constitution Where your Central Bank does
написали Конституцию Где ваш Центробанк
not obey your
не подчиняется вашим
authorities, see that the Central Bank does not
властям смотри что Центробанк не
obey your
подчиняется вашим
authorities, it blows instructions from some
властям дует указаниям каких-то там
international type of banks Yes, where is this  in the
международных типа банков Да где такое в
Constitution, I checked it, I think maybe
Конституции вот я проверил я думаю может
I didn’t study the Constitution of the Russian
я плохо изучал Конституцию Российской
Federation well, I’m still a lawyer and I was
Федерации Я всё-таки юрист и мне
interested in the Constitutions of different countries,
интересно было Конституции разных стран
I also studied the Constitution of the
я в том числе изучал Конституцию
Russian Federation, so I thought maybe
Российской Федерации вот я подумал может
something was wrong, we opened
что-то не так мы с вами открыли
the Constitution and found  mentioning the
Конституцию и нашли упоминание центра
Bank center in the Constitution three times the first time
Банка в Конституции три раза первый раз
about the issue of the ruble super the second time that the
про эмиссию рубля супер второй раз что
president nominates the candidacy of the head of the
президент вносит кандидатуру главы
chairman of the Central Bank to the State Duma and
председателя Центробанка в Госдуму и
also removes the head of the Central Bank from office
также отстраняет от должности главы
Yes, and the State Duma
Центробанка Да а Государственная Дума
approves the candidacy of the head of the Central Bank
утверждает кандидатуру главы Центробанка
Yes the chairman the question turns out that
Да председателя вопрос получается что
the head of the Central Bank is
главу Центробанка
appointed
назначает
and dismissed by you  power, your
и увольняет ваша власть ваша
power is nowhere else in the Constitution.
власть нигде в Конституции больше нет
What appoints them, central banks, owls of
Что назначает их э центробанков сов
some Anglo-Saxon, nowhere in the Constitution
какие-то англосакс нигде в Конституции
is there anything that they are obliged to listen to
нет что они обязаны там что-то слушать
someone, and so on. Yes, the question is,
кого-то и так дальше Да вопрос
is it your power that is responsible for the work of the Central Bank or
есть ваша власть или
not? I think  what is not If you are a lawyer
нет Я считаю что нет Если вы юрист
Let me comment on
Позвольте мне прокомментировать
article p of
статью п
the Constitution, the basics of the Constitution,
Конституции основы Конституции р
please comment that this applies Yes,
пожалуйста что это распространяется Да
and you wanted to comment Let’s
и вы хотели про комментирование Давайте
Ask there are
Спросите там
four there are four parts Let’s what
четы там четыре части Давайте вот что
you are interested in
вас интересует
specifically read your Gumi
конкретно зачитайте своми Гуми прин
necessary legal system if
доится е правовой сист если
established by an international treaty
международным договором установлены иные
rules are different from those provided for by the laws, then the
правила чем предусмотренные законы то
rules of international law are applied
применяется правила международного права
correctly, I quote, see this is the
правильно про котирую смотрите это
normal practice of different states
нормальная практика разных государств
if Russia Yes, for example,
если Россия Да например
joined some kind of
присоединилась к какому-то
international treaty Yes, not just for
международному договору Да не просто
example Japan and America agreed on ITO
например Япония с Америкой о мто
and the main thing for Russia is not
договорились и главным для России нет
only those agreements Yes to  which Russia
только те договоры Да к которым Россия
has joined, if Russia, for example,
присоединилась если Россия например
has acceded to a treaty there on the
присоединилось к договору там о
recognition of some kind of convention, and then the
признании о какой-то конвенции да то
actions of this convention extend
действия этой конвенции распространяются
to the territory of Russia. Absolutely true,
на территорию России Абсолютно верно
if
если
Russia does this, if Russia does not
Россия это делает если Россия не
recognize this treaty, for example,
признаёт этот договор например
it does not accede to some
там не присоединяется к какому-то
treaty on nuclear proliferation
договору о распространении ядерного
weapons does not apply if
оружия на не распространяется если
Russia accedes to an international
Россия присоединяется к международному
treaty on the mutual extradition of
договору о взаимной выдаче там
criminals there, yes, yes it
криминальных преступников да то да
does apply if a person is caught on
действует если человека поймали на
the territory of the Russian Federation Yes, but he
территории Российской Федерации Да а он
committed a crime in France, yes, for
сделал преступление во Франции да то
example, yes, he is extradited to
например да его выдают во
France, what’s wrong with you
Францию что что вам не
Well, everything turns out  the whole question In the
так Ну получается Всё весь вопрос В
agreements that we signed and
договорах который мы подписывали да
which one look which agreement Write
какой смотрите какой договор Напишите
stop Write to tell me what kind of
стоп Напишите на скажите мне какой какой
agreement your Central Bank forced you to
договор вас заставил ваш Центробанк Да
keep gold and foreign exchange reserves abroad
держать золотовалютные резервы за границ
what kind of agreement I don’t know such an agreement such an
какой договор я такого договора не знаю
agreement does not
такого договора не
exist Maybe you are right Yes but
существует Может быть вы правы Да но тем
nevertheless  less Yes, here in this article it
не менее Да вот здесь в этой статье
makes sense that we obey
имеется смысл в том что мы подчиняемся
me still does not respect without subordinating no no
мне всё равно ещё не почит не подчиняя
no no do not obey the Anglo-Saxons,
нет нет нет нет не подчиняйся англосакс
including the Anglo-Saxons, obey the
а в том числи англосаксы подчиняются
international treaties that they
международным договорам которые они
agreed upon If you and the Anglo-Saxons
согласовали Если вы и англосаксы да
accept, for example, some  treaties of
принимаете например какие-то договора
maritime law yes About not attacking
морского права да О не нападении там на
civilian ships there And so on, yes then this
гражданские суда И так дальше да то это
is part of your legislative
есть часть вашей тоже законодательной
system, part of your legislation,
системы часть вашего законодательства
you understand Stein,
понимаете Штейн
now
теперь
the question is
вопрос
who forced the Central Bank to
кто заставил Центральный банк
keep funds
держать средства за
abroad, then if it was not Putin who did this,
границей дальше если это делал не Путин
not your government, then
не ваша власть то
why after  how
почему после того как
these funds were seized abroad
эти средства были арестованы за границе
Why was the head of the National Bank not
Почему главу Национального банка не
fired or removed from office Although this is
уволили не сместили с должности Хотя это
within the prerogatives of the president We
в прерогативы президента Мы же
looked in article 0 now no in
посмотрели в статье 0 сечас нет в
article 83 yes the president Yes, uh, raises
статье 83 да президент Да ээ ставит
before the State Duma the question of
перед государственнной думой вопрос об
vacating the post of chairman of the
освобождении должности председателя
Central Bank of Russia  The Federation
Центрального банка Российской Федерации
and the State Duma are releasing him from this
и Госдума его освобождает от этой
position. Yes, why has it been more than two
должности Да почему вот уже больше дву
years since
лет как
the Anglo-Saxons brazenly,
англосаксы нагло
indisputably, unceremoniously took away your
бесспорно бесцеремонно забрали ваши
gold and foreign exchange reserves, seized them
золотовалютные резервы наложили на них
and are now giving them to Ukraine?
арест и сейчас отдают их Украине
Why, none of the Russian officials are
Почему никто из российских чиновников ни
the head of the National Bank
глава Нацбанка
Yes, your Central Bank Yes, the chairman, neither
Да Центробанка вашего Да председатель ни
Putin nor  The State Duma Yes, it didn’t suffer any
Путин ни Госдума Да не понесла никакого
punishment Who among your
наказания Кто виноват из ваших
officials is to blame for
чиновников в
this Well, for the most part Well, as it
этом Ну по большей части Ну как мне
seems to me, the system that was originally
кажется система изначально которая
built I think it’s the same in yours
построена Мне кажется она и у вас такая
Well, in general, Let’s talk about
же Ну вот в целом Давайте буду про
Russia more Well, I don’t know what to say,
Россию больше Ну говорить я не знаю
you’ll find  yourself or this is a mirror or you won’t
найдёте вы у себя или это зеркало или Не
find it Well, it’s your right already with us
найдёте Ну это Ваше право уже у нас
to get into power, well, you need a lot, you
чтобы попасть во власть ну нужно большие
need a lot of money Well, or some kind of
нужны большие деньги Ну либо какие-то
connections with business Yes, business rules one way
связи с бизнесом Да бизнес правит так
or another, how is it profitable for them, they invest
или иначе как Им выгодно они вкладывают
money in the advertising campaign of this
деньги в рекламную кампанию этого
deputy and  he actually
депутата и он собственно говоря
speaks Yes and if you don’t have money then
выступает Да и если у тебя нет денег то
you won’t advance
ты не продвинется
Putin No there is that well
Путин Нет там в том что
Nago opinion No on the fact that
ну Наго мнения Нет по поводу того что
Why did Yelna decide to choose him Yes but how
Почему ельна решил его выбрать Да а как
not how did he even how did he get to the
не как он вообще как он попал в
prime minister Tell Tell  Yes,
премьер-министр Расскажите Расскажите Да
it’s interesting that it was
интересно это
known that whoever has money could
во было что кто имеет бабки тот смог
become a deputy, a minister, an official,
ставать депутатом министром чиновником
like Vladimir
как Владимир
Putin, without money, he became just a young
Путин без денег стал просто молодой
guy. Yes, he became the
парнишка Да стал
prime minister, this is the
премьер-министром это
greatest official,
величайшие чиновник
that he was an FSB officer, he was already a FSB officer
что он фсбшником фсбшником был уже
from the very beginning. Well, he’s a poor ordinary FSB officer. Yes, what’s
изначально Ну он бедный обычный фсбшник
his name?  they did as he was made
Да как как его сделали как его сделали
prime minister
премьер-министром
Well, if eln has certain
Ну если ельн имеет у себя определенные
power structures Yes, Vla’s structure, excuse me, yes, a
структуры власти Да структу Вла извините
definition of the structure from where he can
да определ структуры откуда он может
take people, he Perhaps in Putin he saw
брать людей он Возможно в Путине увидел
just the person who wanted to revive
как раз человек который хотел возродить
Russia at the extreme rate under NM, the war
Россию по крайне ре при НМ война
ended with him becoming you  do you want to say
закончилась ен став вы хотите сказать
that Yeltsin, who was ruled by the
что Ельцин которым управляли
Anglos, who wrote
англо которые написали ельцину
the Constitution for Yeltsin, some in
Конституцию кое
front of whom Yeltsin danced the Kalinka
перед которыми ельн танцевал Калинку
Malinka, and this Yeltsin, who didn’t take a single step,
малинку и этот Ельцин который ни шагу не
with the permission of the
делал С позволения
Anglo-Saxons, put Putin
англосаксов поставил Путина
as prime minister, it’s quite possible if at
премьером вполне возможно если он в
some point he realized that his country was coming apart
какой-то момент понял что он страна идёт
at the seams and he  I still wanted to
по швам и он захотел её всё-таки
preserve it as a Russian
сохранить как русский
person, you know, the Anglo-Saxons have everything from
человек понимаете англосаксы всё у
Yeltsin Yes, the entire presidential apparatus yes In
Ельцина Да весь аппарат президентский да
short, everyone in the Duma was a protege of
Все короче в Думе все были ставленник
the Anglo-Saxons yes The question turns out that
англосаксов да Вопрос получается что
the Anglo-Saxons specifically took and
англосаксы да специально взяли и
installed Putin
поставили через Ельцина поставили Путина
as Prime Minister through Yeltsin
премьером
Well, perhaps this is also possible if
так Ну возможно такое тоже Возможно если
they say  a certain thesis is that a person is
сказа определённые тезис что человек м
well-
ну
gendered, we know. The fact is that I studied I
полу мы знаем Дело в том что я изучал Я
studied these topics of the Anglo-Saxons
изучал вот эти темы англосаксов
Bilderberg clubs Golden Billion
бильдербергский клубы Золотой миллиард
Yes, sovereign
Да суверенное
right, I’ll tell you, I have 18 years of practice,
право я вам скажу у меня 18 лет практики
so in 2 years there will be a
поэтому через 2 года будет
twentieth Saxons Not for any position Not
двадцатого саксы Ни на одну должность Ни
for one  they don’t put a random person,
на одну не ставят случайного человека
everyone whom the Anglo-Saxons put in
все кого проставлять англосаксы на
any positions were either direct
какие-то должности были либо прямой
agents of the Anglo-Saxon world or were
агентуры англосаксонского мира либо были
recruited by the Anglo-Saxon world. Yes,
завербован англосаксонский миром Да
and
и
Putin, you know where he served. He
Путин вы же знаете где он Служил он
served in the GDR in Germany. So nearby, through the
Служил в ГДР в Германии так рядом Через
Berlin Wall there was a huge
Берлинскую стену была огромнейшая
intelligence network of the United States.
агентурная сеть Соединённых Штатов
America, that is, the Anglo-Saxon
Америки то есть англосакс
If you remember there was such a Stasi Agent
Если вы вспомните была такая Агент штази
angel
ангела
Angela called
Анжела называли
Merkel who,
Меркель которая
through
через
her internal abilities of persuasion
свои внутренние способности к убеждению
and quite a good young
и довольно неплохую юную
chest,
грудь
recruited Vladimir Putin about this for
завербовал Владимира Путина об этом уже
a long time already I have, now you speak English
давно есть я вот вы английским владеете
or
или
German Well, I understand English to some extent
немецким Ну английским в какой-то мере
I'm doing The fact is that I
понял я дела В том что я и английский
know English well and I
хорошо знаю английский свободно и на
read German fluently Yes, I got acquainted with the
немецком читаю Да я ознакомился с де в
fact that
том что
last year they opened the statute of
в прошлом году открыли истёк срок
limitations for these documents, the Stasi opened
давности этих документов штази открыли
the archives of the Stasi intelligence of this Groves and
архивы штази разведки этой гровс и там
it’s all there, it’s no longer a secret
всё это есть это уже никому не секрет
why did they replace Angela Merkel in Germany?
почему в Германии сместили ангелу
Yes, because it emerged then that
Меркель Да потому что всплыло тогда что
she
ээ она
had a
имела
rather unconventional warm relationship
довольно нетрадиционные тёплые отношения
with the young gebis Vladimir Putin
ээ с молодым геби сом Владимиром Путиным
for the purpose of recruiting him for American
с целью его вербовки на американскую
NATO intelligence. And you know that then the
натовскую разведку А вы знаете что тогда
main European branch of the
главная европейская отделение филиала
CIA branch was based across the Berlin Wall?
ЦРУ да
at number 14 Yes, and his military department was
под номером 14 Да и его вово отдел как
just engaged in the recruitment of
раз занимался вербовкой
Soviet
советских
officers photographs. If you go
офицеров фотографии Если вы зайдёте
look, if you can
посмотрите если вы на немецком можете
read German, hammer in
читать забейте в
and Vladimir Putin there are photographs, yes,
и Владимир Путин фотографии есть да как
they are kissing in a bar, there are photographs of
в баре они целуются фотографии есть как
them in a safe
они на явочной
house, let’s say they are
квартире скажем
not really engaged  Godly deeds
занимаются не совсем богоугодными делами
in not entirely godly poses and since
в не совсем богоугодных позах и с тех
then
пор
Yes, Vladimir Putin was conducted by English
Да Владимира Путина вела английская
intelligence mi
разведка ми
de
де
ishe and
ише так
so in the same
вот в дено дем
year no ordinary man in the
году никакой простой мужчина на
post-Soviet space could become
постсоветском пространстве не мог стать
prime minister or president,
премьером или президентом никого бы не
even the Anglo-Saxons would not
допустили даже англосаксы не такие чтобы
allow anyone in  they allow
допускать случайных людей они допускают
only those who are with
только тех кто при
them, only those who signed And you know
им только тех кто подписал А вы знаете
what the
чем подписывают договора
Anglo-Saxons sign contracts with, with blood from a
англосаксы кровью кровью с
finger, a person puts a signature and gives
пальца человек ставит роспись и ставит
him a small injection, a
ему делают маленький укол
seal
печать
that seems to me that they took off such gentle povni, the
что мне кажется они такие неж повни
Anglo-Saxons are pressing, the Russian oligarchs swore allegiance to
англосакс российские олигархи присягнули
the Anglo-Saxons, they all hold it on purpose
англосакс все они специально держат
children were sent to study in London Yes,
детей отправляли учиться в лондо Да
their property is in
имущество у них в
London, not on Baikal. It’s true, not on
Лондона не на Байкале Правда не на
Baikal like this because I won’t
Байкале вот так потому что
take a toss
тошку возьму
here. I agree with you, of course they’re not
не тут я с вами согласен само собой не
afraid that they’ll be taken by the scruff of the neck. Well, what are
боятся что их за шкирку возьмут Ну чему
you talking about? So initially you say you’re an
вы ведёте вот изначально вы говорите ти
Agent of Germany  and what’s next for Germany Don’t
Агент Германии и что дальше Германии Не
look Not Germany
смотрите Не Германии
Germany I don’t understand I explain I explain
Германия не понимаю объясняю объясняю
look Germany Germany in
смотрите Германия Германия в сорок пятом
1945 ceased to exist as a
году прекратила существование как
subject of international law, yes it
субъект международного права да она
became a puppet state in the hands of
стала марионеточный государством в руках
the Anglo-Saxons Yes, there is no independent one,
англосаксов Да нет никакой независимой
you see, Germany’s policy is completely
вы же видите политика Германии полностью
dependent on the policy of the States, now it’s true
зависит от политики Штатов сейчас правда
it’s Puppets they put there Scholz
это Марионетки они ставят там шольц
Merkel Yes, it’s all just short-
Меркель Да это всё просто короче
speaking heads what the states will say the states
говорящие головы что скажут штаты штаты
like Pressed a button Scholz says
как Нажали на кнопочку шольц говорит
Pressed another button Scholz is silent
Нажали на другую кнопочку шольц молчит
all of this It’s obvious I don’t know You
всё это Это очевидно я не знаю Вы же это
see it too You seem like a smart person
видите тоже вы вроде умный человек
really you should see  that Germany is not
правда вы должны видеть что Германия не
on its own not on its own Yes, and it
самостоятельно не самостоятельно Да и
turns out
получается
that Putin
что Путин
Germany was just a layer, yes,
Германия была просто прослойкой да
because NATO bases were in
потому что натовские базы стояли в
Germany Yes, all the agents were in Germany,
Германии Да агентура вся была в Германии
it was just such a layer and the
просто это была прослойка такая и
Anglo-Saxons were
англосаксы
the Anglo-Saxons when the Soviet
англосаксы когда развалили Советский
Union collapsed, the greatest power that
Союз величайшую державу которая
launched Yuri Gagarin himself into space  the
запустила в космос самого Юрия Гагарина
first person in the world And before that
первого человека в мире А до этого
they launched the first two dogs in the world Belka
запускали первых двух собак в мире Белку
and Strelka, you know about Belka and Strelka
и Стрелку знаете про Белку и Стрелку
they were the first Soviet dogs the first ones to
это были первые советские собаки первые
successfully fly into space
успешно слетали в космос
for the first time not just some
впервые не какие-то там кенгуру
Australian kangaroos Yes not some
австралийские Да не какие-то
South American Asumas not a grizzly bear
южноамериканские асумы не медведь гризли
flew  and Belka and Strelka are our simple
полетел а Белка и Стрелка наши простые
Soviet ones, not some kind of you know how
советские не какие-то там знаете как
now these are super thoroughbred expensive
сейчас эти там супер породистые дорогие
ordinary two mongrels they took they lived at the
обычные две дворняги взяли они жили на
cosmodrome and they were the first to be allowed into space
космодроме и их пустили первых в космос
and tested and the monument to Belka and Strelka is the one
на испытали и памятник белки и стрелки
hundred and first dogs cosmonauts to whom
сто первые собаки космонавты которым
humanity erected a monument they  from the
человечество поставило памятник они из
Soviet Union and the Americans then
Советского Союза и американцы тогда
the Anglo-Saxons said that we will not
англосаксы сказали что мы это не
forgive the Soviet Union for this. They understood
простим Советскому Союзу Они поняли
the enormous potential of our Soviet
огромнейший потенциал нашей Советской
Motherland and you know the Zbigniew Obzhinka plan.
Родины и вы знаете план збигнева обжинки
Yes, the big chessboard and the
Да большая шахматная доска и План
Marshal's Plan for the collapse of the Soviet Union,
Маршала по развалу Советского Союза
you know when they were written. The fact is that I
знаете когда писались Дело в том что я
studied it I  I The fact is that here
изучал это я Я Дело в том что вот я
I am in 1981, I
восемьдесят первого года я ещё в
was born in the Soviet Union. What year were you
Советском Союзе родился Вы какого года
born 0 0 You see Yes, you are unlucky to have
рождения 0 0 видите Да вам не повезло
lived yet, but I have lived. I lived in the USSR and
ещё пожить а Я пожил Я пожил в СССР и
now I see how people were there in the USSR.
сейчас смотрю насколько там в СССР были
Man is a friend to man and now
люди Человек человеку друг а сейчас
Man is a wolf to man, you know, and the
Человек человеку волк понимаете и
Americans imposed this, they imposed it
американцы это же навязали они навязали
first on Hollywood films, and our
сначала фильмы голливудские да наши
Soviet films were watch The
советские фильмы были смотрите
Diamond Arm, true love Friendship,
Бриллиантовая рука правда любовь Дружба
mutual assistance is sacred, just look at the
взаимовыручка святое прям а посмотрите
American Rimbaud Terminator murder
американские Рембо Терминатор убийство
shoot all this, they imposed
стреляют всё это же они навязали
cruelty on ours in the nineties
жестокость в наш в девяностых годах
when they ruined They  they specially
когда они развалили Они специально
filled the entire video salon and young people
заполнили всё видеосалон и молодёжь
looked at the looks of these American
смотрела на смотрится этих американских
militants, take Turbo chewing gum and
боевиков возьмёт жвачку Турбо Да и
go
пойдёт
shoot, let’s go beat each other, in
стрелять пошли бить друг другу у нас в
Soviet society we didn’t have that, people
Советском обществе не было такого люди
gathered for philosophical
собирались на философские
circles, talked about the
кружки разговаривали о
prevailing
ээ превалирующее
essence of being over consciousness, that it is
сутью бытия над сознанием что оно есть
primary
первичное
in me  school during political information lessons
меня в школе на уроках полити информации
he was on Wednesday lesson zero I remember
он был в среду нулевым уроком Я помню
a third grader I was preparing
третьеклассник я готовил
a report on how our hockey players tore
доклад о том как наши хоккеисты порвали
other hockey players I was proud of our union
других хоккеистов я был горд за наш союз
for our hockey players And now the youth
за наших хоккеистов А сейчас молодёжь
that they sit on the American Internet
что она сидит в американских интернетах
watch American films American
смотрит американские фильмы американские
cartoons go to  American
мультики ходит в американских
jeans were sold for jeans, you don’t even
джинсах продали за джинсы вы хоть нен
wear them from time to time, mostly wearing
носите периодически быва в основном
shorts You know that I understood your
шорт Вы знаете что я понял вашу
idea Tell me, to be honest, I don’t
мысль Расскажите Вот честно говор Не
understand. It seems to me that you seem to be on the
пойму Мне кажется вы как будто бы и на
side of the world, God willing, I really have
стороне ского мира вот дай Бог правда я
at least a little bit of such
хотя бы немножко такую
inserts from ours  If you are reading
вставок с нашего Если вы читаете
Slavic
славянин
Slavic look I
славянин смотрите я
do look I am generally an anti-globalist
делать смотрите Я вообще антиглобалист
yes but in Ukraine we can’t talk about it
да но у нас в Украине нельзя про это
yes Because if we
говорить да Потому что если мы будем
talk like if I were on the street so at
говорить вот если б я на улице так вы
least you don’t
хоть не
write down not in any case not everything
записываете не ни в ком случае не всё
because if  for example, here the SBU
потому что если например у нас там СБУ
knows that I openly talk about
знает что я открыто говорю про
the Anglo-Saxons against them and they will bring me
англосаксов против них да меня привлекут
to justice, we can’t have
к ответственности у нас нельзя
the Anglo-Saxons clamping down on everything so much. Yes, any
англосаксы настолько зажали всё Да любая
journalist, if he says something about
журналист Если что-то скажет про
the Anglo-Saxons, he will immediately be fired from us even
англосаксы его сразу увольняет у нас ещё
more harshly than you let the Anglo-Saxons in Russia
жёстче чем у вас в России англосаксы
the roots you understand are just tough
пустили корни понимаете просто жесть так
so
вот
uh that I forgot about the Soviet Union that I
ээ что я про Советский Союз забыл что я
already said where I stopped I’m
уже говорил на чём Я остановился
sorry yes and jeans jeans so
извините да а джинсы джинсы так вот
look Why you can’t wear jeans yes
смотрите Почему нельзя носить джинсы да
Because
Потому
you read international law and
что международное право Вы же читали да
that it prevails over Russian
что оно превалирует над российским
legislation as well  over the Ukrainian
законодательством также и над украинским
they came up with such
они придумали такое право
intellectual property rights and patents
интеллектуальной собственности и патенты
and you know that the jeans are patented
и вы знаете что джинсы запатентованы
Yes, the
Да
manufacturer and his heirs were
производителем и его наследниками был
such Levi Ostrich, so he invented jeans,
такой Леви страус так он придумал джинсы
he patented them and not a single manufacturer
он запатентовал и ни один производитель
in the world has the right to produce jeans
не имеет права в мире выпускать джинсы
without making a contribution
без отчисления
to the Levi
в фирму Леви
Ostrich company If you  you buy jeans Yes 20%
страуса Если вы покупаете джинсы Да 20%
20% of the cost of your Jeans Yes the
20% стоимости ваших Джинс Да
manufacturer sends
производитель отправляет на
it to America Levi Ostrich you understand how
ээ в Америку Леви страус вы поняли как
they instilled in us their culture of
они насадили насадили нам свою культуру
wearing jeans so it’s just just
носить джинсы так это просто просто
tough
жесть
I’ll show you
я вам сейчас покажу
a minute with our business
минутку нашим бизнесом
Yes look I’m also wearing jeans by the way
Да вот смотрите Я кстати тоже в джинсах
but with us, it’s just that if you don’t wear
но у нас просто если ты будешь ходить не
jeans, then Well, they’ll ask, Why do
в джинсах то Ну спросят А почему ты
n’t you wear
ходишь не в
jeans? We know
джинсах У нас знаете
Seriously,
Серьёзно
what’s on You say Yes, I’m seriously saying
что да на Говорите Да я серьёзно говорю
Look, the fact is that when you go into our stores, it
Смотри де в том что у нас в магазинах
costs Coca-Cola, you can’t
заходишь стоит coca-cola ты не можешь
if you're a store, you can't help but
если ты магазин ты не можешь не
sell Coca-Cola Yes, if you're wearing jeans
продавать кока-колу Да если ты в джинса
Yes, except for Jeans, only these officials are allowed to
Да кроме Джинс разрешают только вот этим
wear trousers. Yes, if so, for
чиновникам в брюках ходить Да если так Я
example, I'll walk down the street in shorts,
например буду идти по улице э в шортах а
or in trousers, a patrol can stop me
или в брюках меня может остановить
and Just ask  why don’t you
патруль и Просто спроси а почему вы не
use jeans and what will I say that I
пользуетесь джинсами и что я скажу что я
don’t want to pay the Anglo-Saxons will take me to the basement
не хочу платить англосакс меня на подвал
I don’t want that, so
заберут Я такого не хочу так вот
look at our Slavic shirts, you
смотрите наши славянские рубахи вы
know what they
знаете какие
were like. You’re a Slav. What are
были Вот вы славянин Какие вот смотрите
the Anglo-Saxons looking at now? Yes, they want. What’s the
сейчас англосаксы Да они хотят В чём
trick of the Anglo-Saxons?  they want globalization
фишка англосаксов они хотят глобализацию
they want to erase all national
они хотят стереть все национальные
differences Yes they prohibit Yes the
различия Да они Запрещают Да
use of national clothes
использовать национальные одежды Вот
For example for the Russians Yes for the Russians
например россиянам Да россиянам
the Anglo-Saxons erased the national memory
англосаксы стёрли национальную память
100 years ago You had these kings
ещё 100 лет назад У вас же вот эти цари
they were the Germans yes Peter I
были они же Немцы были да Пётр I
Katerina
Катерина
really the Germans Well Serve and and  and
правда немцы Ну вот Служи и и и
look So with us We were still able to
посмотрите Так у нас у нас Мы ещё смогли
preserve our Slavic robes,
сохранить наши славянские одеяния
look, look at these Slavic
посмотри посмотри вот эти славянские
magical symbols Yes, they carry the spirit of
магические символы Да они несут дух
our Slavic family Yes, you
нашего рода Славянского Да ты ни одного
will not see a single Anglo-Saxon with such symbols, it’s
англосакс не увидишь с такими символами
true You once saw the Anglo-Saxon
правда Ты видел когда-то англосакс
queen of Britain with such
королеву Британии с такими
symbols  I haven’t seen it, so no, and what they
символами не видел так вот нет и что они
did in Russia, yes, you can
сделали в России да вот ты можешь
name it in Russia, you have these
назвать в России есть у вас вот такие
Slavic attires, no,
одеяния славянские нету уже
really, yes, we have it anyway, we don’t have it,
правда да есть по-любому не у нас есть
where do you have it or not, well, the movement
где вот у тебя есть или нет ну движение
of such a Russian
такого российского
sa
са
EU  The Soviet Union and polo
ЕС Советского Союза и поло
is Spider-Man, this is generally
есть Человек паук это вообще
from Schat, these are the ones we used to wear,
из щать вот эти мы ходили раньше
embroidered shirts, now the Anglo-Saxons say no, you
вышиванка сейчас англосакс говорят нет
have to wear jackets so that everyone can be
надо ходить в пиджаках чтобы были все
like these English Sarah frag jacket,
как вот эти английские Сары фраг пиджак
that’s their uniform, black in black,
это ж ихняя форма чёрная в чёрный цвет
the Slavs didn’t wear black,
славяне в чёрном не ходили
really, you  I once saw Slavs
правда Ты видел когда-то чтобы славяне
walking around in black
ходили в чёрных
jackets, there was no such thing, so
пиджаках не было такого так вот
look, so you, because you are
смотри Так ты потому что тебя славянина
already being made a Slav in Pika, go,
уже делают в Пике ходи
I have five of these embroidered
У меня есть пять Вот таких вышитых
Slavic grunts, and if they find out
славянских рубак и если у меня узнают
that I am holding them, five of them should come to me too  there
что я их держу пять штук ко мне тоже
will be questions, do you honor the national
будут вопросы ты что чти национальные
Slavic traditions, they will immediately
славянские традиции сразу будут
ask No, they want to make everyone the
спрашивать Нет они хотят всех сделать
same, the Russians have already done this,
одинаковыми россиян уже сделали вот у
you don’t have anyone, look at our
вас нету ни у кого смотри наши
Slavic
славянские
symbols, you see what our great Slavs
символы видишь Как пра наши славяне
wore, I’ll show you even more It’s
носили я тебе ещё больше покажу Это
just a very Secret
просто это очень Тайная
collection,
коллекция
look what  you
смотри что ты
see a shirt I don’t know the ancient symbol of
видишь рубаху Я не знаю древний символ
Kolovrat
коловрата
Slavic right-handed left-handed
Славянский правосторонний левосторонний
for this for this shirt for this shirt
вот за эту за эту рубашку за эту рубаху
you can’t go out into the street in it
её в ней на улицу нельзя выходить нельзя
because they’ll immediately ask Are you honoring
потому что сразу спросят Ты что
Slavic symbols? I wear it at home
славянские символы чти по Я дома её
But also a shirt, look at
одеваю А вот тоже рубаха смотри
Slavic ornaments
славянские орнаменты
The Anglo-Saxons want us Ukrainians to
англосаксы хотят чтобы мы украинцы тоже
be like you Russians. Now, without without, we have
были как вы россияне Сейчас без без
abandoned the Slavic everything. You
отказались от Славянского всего у вас же
don’t already have it, you already understand when in the nineties and
нету уже понимаешь когда в девяностых
nineties. Yes, you also had some
девяностых Да ещё у вас были какие-то
movements that wanted to revive
движения которые хотели возрождать
some Slavic traditions. Yes, they were all
славянские какие-то традиции Да всё их
hushed up because  Yeltsin issued a decree If
замяли потому что Ельцин издал указ Если
you look at the
ты посмотришь
decree in October 92, it was issued, but I don’t
указ в октябре 92 года был издан да не
remember its number, but it was appointed about the
помню его номер но он назначался о
pernicious influence of national traditions
тлетворное влиянии национальных традиций
and they decided that
и там постановили да что
uh the governor and the mayors of cities
ээ губернатором Да и мэром городов
should strengthen work with the tendencies uh that
усилить работу с тенденциями ээ что
young people are beginning to return to
молодёжь начинает возвращаться к
traditions and seek  some Russian
традициям и искать какие-то русские
kosovorotki, kokoshniks, bast shoes and balalaikas
косоворотки кокошники лапти да балалайки
so that all this wouldn’t happen because
чтобы этого всего не было потому что
the Anglo-Saxons want you to forget history, you
англосаксы хотят чтоб забыли историю вы
Russians have already forgotten their history, all
россияне уже забыли свою историю всё
the Anglo-Saxons come, you understand, for example, they
англосаксы приходят понимаешь например
say where is the history of your people, where are
говорят где история вашего народа где
your embroidered Slavic shirts? You still
ваши вышитые славянские рубахи Вы таки
don’t, everything they say means that  our
нету всё они говорят это значит наша
Earth, we forgot that we won in the
Земля мы забыли что мы выиграли во
Second World War You forgot that you
Второй мировой войне Вы забыли что вы
won in the Second World War and
выиграли во Второй мировой войне а то
what you are now showing me is what
что ты сейчас мне показываешь это что
your government is imposing on you
вам навязывает твоё правительство
because it allows you to fight between discord within
зе что позволяет рать меж рознь внутри
your country You have Russians living
вашей страны У вас есть живут русские
Romanians living You  such good fellows Let's
живут румыны Вы такие молодцы Давайте
promote Ukraine Let's for
украинство продвигать Давайте вот ни с
no reason the Romanians are like this they are
того ни с сего румыны они такие вот они
niche rank in our country and Russian niche
ниши ранг в нашей стране и русские ниши
rank in our country that's what you're
ранг в нашей стране вот то что сейчас
telling me now This is the key thing that
мне рассказываешь это вот Ключевое это
shows what's happening in your country
показывает вот то что у вас стране
What's happening  there is Ukraine, it is
Происходит что вот есть украинство
defined above all and all
определ оно превыше всего а все
other races are
остальные расы они
lower We don’t have that, yes you’re right, we
ниже У нас такого нет да ты прав у нас
don’t have that kind of races And we have
такого не какие расы А у нас есть
Bashkirs we have I do
башкиры у
n’t know who Tatars I don’t
на у нас есть не знаю кого татары не
know Ukrainians including We do
знаю украинцы в том числе У нас такого
n’t have that  there is a certain race
нет что есть какая-то определённая раса
and it is admirable, so by the way, look,
и она превозно так вот кстати смотри
the Anglo-Saxons, the Anglo-Saxons, forced you to destroy the
англосакс англосакс заставили вас
Russians. Yes, to destroy other nations,
россиян Да уничтожать другие народы
for example, they closed all Ukrainian schools in
например закрыли все украинские школы в
Russia, there is not a single
России не не осталось ни одной
Ukrainian school left. Show me where Vassi
украинской школы Покажи где у васси
started telling there, he didn’t come
начал там рассказывать никчему не пришёл
just about where-  then he told Germany that
просто про где-то Германии рассказал что
why Germany started all this, I still don’t
чему Германия начала всё это я так и не
understand, I started telling you about it from your shirt.
понял начал про с рубашки рассказывать
Listen to yourself. Look at
ты несёшь Послушай себя Ты посмотри у
us, we fought to the last to
нас да мы до последнего боролись чтобы у
have Russian-language schools and they were
нас были русскоязычные школы и они были
until the Anglo-Saxons forced Putin to
пока англосаксы не заставили Путина
attack us and  the Anglo-Saxons in Russia
напасть на нас а англосаксы в России
forced Putin to close all Ukrainian
заставили Путина закрыть все украинские
schools there is not a single one look name at least
школы нет ни одной посмотри назови хоть
one Ukrainian school there are 5 million
одну украинскую школу живёт 5 млн
Ukrainians living 5 million in the Russian
украинцев 5 миллионов в Российской
Federation where At least one
Федерации где Хоть одна
school where at least one Ukrainian school in the
школа где Хоть одна школа украинская в
Russian
Российской
Federation the shame of the Slavic people is
Федерации позор Славянского народа - это
Ukraine Unfortunately
Украина К сожалению
you I do  I thought I thought that you were our
ты Я ду Я думал Я думал что ты наш
Slav and you sold out to the Anglo-Saxons, you yourself are an
славянин а ты продался англосакс ты сам
Anglo-Saxon, I understood you are Anglo, you are
англосакс я понял ты англо ты
Anglo-Saxon, I understood Yes,
англосаксонская понял Да ты просто вы
you just sold out. The Anglo-Saxons rewrote their Constitution, you rewrote the Constitution to suit the Anglo-Saxons. Yes, you let the Anglo-Saxons write their own Constitution, look. You
написать себе Конституцию посмотри Ты
yourself read that you are international  wrote
сам читал что международный вы написали
that international treaties are higher than your
что международные договора выше ваших
Russian sovereign laws You
российских суверенных законов Всё вы
sold everything, you betrayed the Slavic Brotherhood,
продали вы предали Славянское Братство
you understand when in
понимаешь когда в
your Yeltsin and Sh Gorv our
ваш Ельцин и ш горв развалили наш
Slavic Soviet Union was destroyed where all the
Славянский Советский Союз где были все
Slavs were living together, the Estonians, the Kazakhs, the
славяне жили дружно эстонцы казахи
Uzbeks, the Ukrainians were all Slavs
узбеки украинцы все были славяне
normally, 15 Slavic republics were
нормально 15 славянских республик было
understandable and you understand
понимаешь а вы
you understand everything and you now you
всё понимаешь ты и вы сейчас вы ничего
didn’t run away
не убежал
like that with a psycho And that’s how we
вот так с психом И вот так
like the squeak comment it was a
ием лайк писка комент це была
divine
божественна
prophet subscribe to my Telegram right
пророчка подпишись на мий Telegram прямо
now axis VN and
зараз ось ВН а
Popik it’s even more and more respectful YouTube
Попик це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube
took us through Scar Georg to your ban and  I
заня нас через Скар Георг в твый бан и
don’t show too much video to people at all times, I don’t show
вдео не показую людям вчасно не показуе
information about streams for this purpose,
информация про стримы тому для того щоб
Mali operational link should be written
ми Мали оперативный звязок пишиться
directly at once and Popik there in telegrams
прямо зараз а Попик там в телеграми
okrim video shchezh tsikava and korisna
окрим видео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and I’m guilty of you trimati
информация и ми повинни з вами тримати
postiyny operational link
постийний оперативный звязок
regardless in that chi show  You're welcome
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Slava Ukraini write
YouTube Слава украини пиши